TU VU Front-end/ Fullstack Web Developer









# **Contact Information**

### **About me**

I am a Junior Software Engineer enthusiastic about developing and problem-solving in software development. Experiences in Web & Android Development, also highly passionate in learning new things to keep up with the cutting edge of technologies. A creative, quick learning, initiative & motivated worker.

# **Personality**

Creativity Adaptability Teamwork Responsibility

### **Hobbies**









Video-game

Volunteer Basketball

Board-game

# **Education**

## 2013 -2018 **Bachelor of Information Technology**

Lapland University of Applied Sciences, Rovaniemi

- A Software Engineer Degree with mainly focus on System Administrator, System Designer & System Developer
- Develop a complete game using Unity in a school's project as a lead software developer

#### 2008 -Luong The Vinh High School for the Gifted 2011

Vietnam

- Department: Information Technology.
- Nominated in Information Technology National Exam 2011.

# Skills

# **Programming**

HTML	React	
CSS	Java	
PHP	Python	
JavaScript	C++	
SQL	Android	
Unity		
Software		
Photoshop	Office	
Git	Blender	
Lunacy		

# **Experiences**

#### 06/2017 -09/2017 **Junior Software Developer**

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

• Create and maintenance a native Windows program to keep track of car rental for a family company.

#### 06/2015 -**Android Developer Trainee** 09/2015

Appro Mobile Co. Ltd., Ho Chi Minh City

- Be part of the development team in a Tax Consulting app for iOS & Android for Korean customer
- Mainly responsible for creating test cases, finding & fixing bugs
- Design a small UI part for Android version.

#### 2012 -12/2013 Web Administrator at [vsava.com]

Vietnam Small Animal Veterinary Association, Ho Chi Minh City

- Managed Vietnam Small Animal Veterinary Association Website
- Mainly responsible for content, user management and website maintanance.